{
    "id": "71f5c839988942128a73e5cf189d7066",
    "title": "Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "They ………………….. him hand and foot and  held him fast.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bound",
                "bind",
                "binding"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "None of them …………………. of doing what he never attempted to do.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "dreamed",
                "dream",
                "dreaming"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "What he ………………….. he could not tell.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "knew",
                "knows",
                "known"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "They .......................................... the roads so that he might not escape.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "guarded",
                "guard",
                "guarding"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He came to my house to tell me what .......................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has happened",
                "had happened",
                "appear"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He promised that no one ............................................. for expressing their opinion.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will be persecuted",
                "would be persecuted",
                "would persecute"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He got his shop .......................................... before the monsoons set in.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "repair",
                "repaired",
                "repairing"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He ran so fast that he .............................................. soon out of breath.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "was",
                "had"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I wonder what he has done with the money I .......................................... him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lend",
                "lent",
                "lending"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It ............................................... to you that he was simply bluffing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "must occur",
                "must have occurred",
                "must occurred"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}